<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="info_how_does_it_work" name="Info Share Accommodation">
            <t t-call="website.layout">

                <div class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section>
                        <div class="container">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-lg-4 col-12 how-to-guides">

                                    <t t-call="pragtech_flatmates_system.info_li_list"/>

                                </div>

                                <div class="col-lg-8 col-12" id="add_html_content">

                                    <div class="container info-page">
                                        <div class="row">
                                            <div class="col-lg-10">
                                                <h1>How does it work?</h1>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">It’s easy to rent out your room or find a place with Flatmates.com.au</h2>
                                                <img src="/pragtech_flatmates_system/static/src/img/find-flatmate.png" class="img-fluid mt-2" alt=""/>
                                                <p class="mt-5">Flatmates.com.au is a peer to peer listing site for those looking for shared homes or those looking for a flatmate. It’s easy to use: simply create a listing, search and connect.</p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><i class="fa fa-pencil-square"></i> <strong>Create a Listing</strong> <br/>
                                                    Whether you’re renting out your spare room or are looking for a new place to live, you’ll need to create a listing. There are two listing types on Flatmates.com.au:</p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><a href="https://flatmates.com.au/list-room"><strong>Property Listing</strong></a><br/>
                                                    Having a property listing is essential for finding a flatmate. A detailed listing should include clear pictures, information about the property and room and a brief description of the other flatmates who live there. To create your listing simply fill in all of the sections and click list my place.</p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><a href="https://flatmates.com.au/room-wanted"><strong>Person Listing</strong></a><br/>
                                                    A person listing, sometimes referred to as a room wanted profile, is the best way to let people know you’re looking for a property. Your person listing should include a little bit about your lifestyle, personality and the kind of place you’re looking for. Adding a photo of yourself to your profile will also increase your response and will place you at the top end of flatmate searches. To create your listing simply fill in the required sections and click save.</p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><i class="fa fa-search"></i> <strong>Search</strong><br/>
                                                    Once you’ve created your listing, it’s time to start your search. It is important to be proactive when searching for a flatmate or a new place because the best rooms and flatmates go quickly. Use the search function to find listings in your preferred area.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    To search, click the white ‘Search share accommodation’ box at the top of the site. Enter a suburb and selected the completed suburb from the suggestions below. You can add five suburbs or one region (Sydney, Melbourne, Brisbane etc). Next select the type of search you’re conducting: Rooms, Flatmates, or Team Up. Then click the green search button.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Advance search filters are found under the Advance Search Filter link at the bottom of the search box. <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Once you have made a search you can favourite it via the ‘Store as saved search’ link at the base of the search box.</p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><i class="fa fa-inbox"></i> <strong>Email alerts</strong><br/>
                                                    Share accommodation is the fastest moving property market with the average listing only lasting 10-14 days and some of the most popular listings only a few hours. To make sure you find out about the best rooms or flatmates we send you email alerts with the latest listings. You can adjust these or turn them off by visiting <a href="https://flatmates.com.au/alerts">Alert Settings</a></p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><i class="fa fa-comment"></i> <strong>Get in Touch</strong><br/>
                                                    If you see a listing you like or a flatmate you think would be perfect, write them a message. When messaging other members about their listing, make sure you have read their details first. Your message should be an introduction about yourself, why you’re interested in the room/flatmate and why you feel you/they would be a great fit for the home. Remember you’ll need to stand out from the other members enquiring, so try to keep it interesting.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    If you’re enquiring directly via a members mobile number, be sure to send them a link to your listing so they can easily find you. Also let them know you found them on Flatmates.com.au. </p>
                                                <div class="mt-4 gray-bx">
                                                    <p><i class="fa fa-lightbulb-o"></i> <strong>Tip</strong><br/>
                                                        Some listings receive a huge number of responses so don’t expect to hear back from every message you send. To avoid disappointment don’t just send one message, make sure you messages all the listings which which could be suitable. If all goes well then you will end up with a number of options to choose from.</p>
                                                </div>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><i class="fa fa-eye"></i> <strong>View</strong> <br/>
                                                    Before you make any decisions or pay any money ensure you conduct a viewing. A viewing is important to not just see the room, but to also meet the flatmates.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    If you cannot meet in person than make a video call on Skype or FaceTime. During the viewing potential flatmates should ask each other questions about lifestyle, habits, work and hobbies. If you have a few contenders for a room, get each potential flatmate around individually. If your plans change and you cannot make it to a viewing please be polite and cancel or reschedule the viewing.</p>
                                                <p class="mt-4"><i class="fa fa-list-ul"></i> <strong>Agreement</strong> <br/>
                                                    Found the right person or place? Be sure to tell them you’re happy and want to proceed. Before moving in go through our <a href="https://flatmates.com.au/info/pre-agreement-checklist">Pre-agreement check list</a>. This will cover everything from bond requirements to house rules. Be sure to also read through our <a href="https://info.flatmates.com.au/legal-introduction">Legal Introduction</a>.</p>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>



                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>