<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="info_frequently_asked_questions" name="Info Share Accommodation">
            <t t-call="website.layout">

                <div class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section>
                        <div class="container">
                            <div class="row">
                                <div class="col-lg-4 col-12 how-to-guides">
                                    <t t-call="pragtech_flatmates_system.info_li_list"/>

                                </div>

                                <div class="col-lg-8 col-12" id="add_html_content">

                                    <div class="container info-page">
                                        <div class="row">
                                            <div class="col-lg-10">
                                                <h1>Frequently Asked Questions</h1>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">If you have a question or need some help, please take a moment to read through our Frequently Asked Questions.</h2>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">How do I activate or edit my listing?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">To activate or edit your listing click Your Account (your name) &gt; then select the listing under ‘Your Listings’ in the centre of the dashboard. At the top of the next page will be a button to Activate.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Edit options appear under each section of the listing.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Photos can also be added and removed in this section at the top.</p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">How can I claim my guarantee?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">Guarantees are applied automatically at the expiration of your purchased plan. To qualify for your guarantee you must have a profile picture, no more than one active property listing and apply for the Guarantee within the same search period.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Should your guarantee not apply and you believe it should have, please <a href="https://flatmates.com.au/contact">contact us</a>. </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">I need help or tenancy advice.</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">The Flatmates.com.au team are unable to provide advice or guidance for individual situations.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    For all the information on tenancies and sharing in your state please see our <a href="https://info.flatmates.com.au/legal-introduction" target="_blank">legal guide section</a>. </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">Do I have to upgrade?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">Flatmates.com.au is a site that can be used for free.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Upgrading allows you to contact all members and view available mobile numbers. Upgrades cannot be held or frozen. For more information please see <a href="https://info.flatmates.com.au/why-upgrade" target="_blank">Why Upgrade</a> </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">I have not received a verification SMS?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">SMS verification can take up to 30 minutes to be delivered depending on your country, or provider. When you receive the code please ensure your code is entered correctly and in full.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    If you close the screen to enter your code, you will need to request a new code. Only the most recently requested code will work.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    If you have not received a verification SMS please <a href="https://flatmates.com.au/contact">contact us</a> with your mobile number (including country code), so we can ensure it was entered into the system correctly. </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">Why is my listing undergoing security checks?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">All new and edited listings go through security checks, formerly known as moderation, to ensure they don’t contain anything prohibited. From time to time, your account may also be checked by our system and team. These checks are to ensure the safety of all members on the site.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    This process should only take a few minutes, however, if anything is picked up by the system it will need to undergo a manual check. Depending on the time of day or the length of the queue, this can take longer to process.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Please be patient, our team will approve your listing as soon as possible. </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">How does the site work? I need help with finding a place or renting my room.</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">For tips on how to use the site and how to list yourself or place, please see our helpful guides.</p>
                                                <p><a href="https://info.flatmates.com.au/how-does-it-work" target="_blank">How does it work</a><br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <a href="https://info.flatmates.com.au/rent-your-spare-room" target="_blank">Tips for finding a flatmate</a><br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <a href="https://info.flatmates.com.au/find-share-accommodation" target="_blank">Tips for finding a room</a></p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">How do I report another member?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">You can report a listing via the “Concerned about this listing” link at the bottom of every listing.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    You can also report a member via the report member link in your messages. Click the three dots in the message header to access this link.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    All feedback is received in confidence.</p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">My payment won’t process.</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">Adblockers can interfere with the payment system. Please disable any Adblocker for our site. Please also ensure you are using the most up-to-date version of your browser and operating system.</p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">I received a message from a member with no profile.</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">Anyone who contacts you via the site is a registered member and have undergone the same verification process as you.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    However, not all members will have a public profile about themselves. Some of these members may have just signed up and verified an account to contact you, so they may not know about a profile until they’ve sent their first message. You can always reply to these members through the messaging system.</p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">When will my listing become Free to Message?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">Your listing will become free to message after 14-days active on the site or when you upgrade your account, whichever is sooner.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    If you have a free account, the listing will automatically become free to message after 14 full days. If you deactivate the listing at any point, the counter will re-start. Flatmates.com.au cannot provide updates or change the date of your listing going free to message.</p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">I have encountered a bug or website issue.</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">If you have a bug or issue to report, please <a href="https://flatmates.com.au/contact">contact us</a>. To help us investigate and resolve the issue as quickly as possible, please also provide us with the device and browser you were using at the time.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Screenshots or URLs are appreciated and may help us identify the issue faster. </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <h2 class="mt-5">Do you have an app?</h2>
                                                <p class="mt-2">We don’t have an app version of the site just yet. However, our site has been optimised and designed for use on mobile browsers. </p>
                                                <hr class="mt-4 mb-4"/>
                                                <p class="mt-5"><strong>If your question hasn’t been answered here, please <a href="https://flatmates.com.au/contact">contact us</a></strong>.<br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Our team are on hand to answer any queries from 9am – 9pm (AEST). </p>


                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>



                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>